

BRENT VANWILDEMEERSCH SOFTWARE ENGINEER

DETAILS

Brussels, Belgium

vanwildemeersch.bre nt@gmail.com

vanwildemeersch.bre nt.github.io

LANGUAGES

Dutch NATIVE French **PROFICIENT FLUENT** English

SKILLS

JS/TS (Vue.js, Angular, React, ReactNative, ES6 Redux, Vuex, Styled Components, Storybook)

HTML5, CSS, LESS/SASS

Cypress, Jest

Git, CI/CD, DevOps basics

Linux and Windows PHP and Wordpress

CERTIFICATIONS

Professional Scrum Master (PSM1)

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

PROFILE

Software engineer with 6 years of experience. A dedicated problem solver and expert skills in JavaScript and supporting languages/libraries and frameworks that solve real world problems through code.

Eager to learn and always open to explore new things

Flexible person who can adapt quickly to changing circumstances

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Problem solver and strong communicator. Eager to prove my value and talent. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through challenging projects. I enjoy working collaboratively, but can run projects independently. Focused on developing scalable and well-documented software solutions

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Media and Communication Technologies

Hogeschool West-Vlaanderen - Kortrijk, Belgium

Industrial Sciences

Vrij Technisch Instituut- Poperinge, Belgium

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (FOR POSITIVE THINKING COMPANY)

November 2020 - Current | Easyfairs

Brussels, Belgium

- Development and maintenance of inhouse products used by clients and by staff
- Development and engineering of prototypes for new features and future
- Improve reliability and customer satisfaction of software applications
- Collaborating with back-end, dev-ops and security team to improve workflows and security
- Development of custom WordPress plugins and themes to facilitate the business

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING CONSULTANT

September 2020 - Current | Positive Thinking Company

Brussels, Belaium

- Guidance of junior Javascript developers in their growth path
- Part of the internal Javascript community
- · Sharing knowledge during KSS (Knowledge Sharing Sessions) about software development, architecture to other consultants, Business Managers, ...
- Conducting technical interviews to assess the skills and abilities of potential candidates

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

July 2017 - August 2020 | Ocular

Zwevezele, Belgium

- Development of audio-visual interactives
 Engineering & architecture of inhouse CMS platform to provide audio-visual interactives of content
- Development of custom CMS platforms as Lead Developer
- Development of custom software solutions

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER (INTERN)

University of the Western Cape

Cape Town, South Africa

- Internship at the Colab for Social Innovation and E-Inclusion
- Development of the University app to create micro-communities on campus
- Guiding starting Computer Science students on their path to become a software developer
- Briefing of stakeholders about upcoming features and releases
- Charity work by giving Java-classes to high-school students around Cape Town.